When you think of a cute, furry wild animal, you often picture a koala.
当你想到一种可爱毛茸茸的野生动物时，脑海里往往会浮现出考拉的样子。
These adorable-looking creatures appear docile and friendly, so it’s no wonder people are concerned about the future of the species after the devastating bushfires that destroyed parts of Australia earlier this year.
这些模样讨人喜欢的动物看起来温顺又友善，所以在今年年初澳大利亚部分地区遭遇毁灭性丛林大火后，人们会担忧这个物种的未来，也就不足为奇了。
Luckily, many survived, which gives us a chance to continue to learn more about these marsupials.
幸运的是，许多考拉幸存了下来，这让我们有机会继续深入了解这些有袋动物。
Australia’s native and unique wildlife such as kangaroos, platypus and koalas, are under constant threat from human activity and natural disasters.
袋鼠、鸭嘴兽、考拉这类澳大利亚本土特有的野生动物，持续面临着人类活动和自然灾害的威胁。
It’s thought at least a billion animals lost their lives as a result of this year’s bushfires.
据悉，今年的丛林大火已导致至少十亿只动物丧生。
Recently, drones and thermal imaging technology have been used to track their movements to help them keep safe.
最近，无人机和热成像技术被用于追踪考拉的行踪，以保障它们的安全。
Protecting these unique species is important because, as The Australian Koala Foundation estimates, there are now possibly as few as 43,000 koalas in the wild.
保护这些独特物种十分重要，因为澳大利亚考拉基金会估计，目前野生考拉的数量可能仅剩下4.3万只。
So, what is so special about koalas and what makes them so ‘cool’?
那么，考拉到底有什么特别之处，又是什么让它们如此“受欢迎”呢？
Maybe we envy their ability to sleep for up to 22 hours day!
或许是我们羡慕它们一天能睡足足22个小时的本事！
Or could it be their laid-back appearance due to the fact that they are herbivores and mainly feed on juicy eucalyptus leaves, which take a lot of time and energy to digest.
又或者是它们那副悠然自得的模样——因为考拉是食草动物，主要以水分充足的桉树叶为食，而消化这些树叶需要耗费大量的时间和精力。
What is amazing is that because they often live in a dry and hot environment, they drink very little water.
令人惊叹的是，由于长期生活在干燥炎热的环境中，考拉的饮水量极少。
So, how do they survive?
那么它们是如何生存的呢？
Well, scientists have discovered that these wild mammals lick running water off the smooth surface of a tree trunk when it is raining.
科学家发现，这种野生哺乳动物会在下雨时，舔食顺着光滑树干流下的雨水。
This phenomenon is called "stemflow".
这种现象被称为“茎流”。
Valentina Mella, the lead author of the research and an ethnologist from the University of Sydney, told the BBC: "I think the main message is that behavioural observations in the wild are very important to establish what is normal and what is unusual, and to truly understand what animals need.
该研究的第一作者、悉尼大学的动物行为学家瓦伦蒂娜·梅拉在接受BBC采访时表示：“我认为核心启示是，野外行为观察对于判断动物行为的正常与异常、真正了解动物需求至关重要。
If we watch them carefully, they will tell us."
只要我们仔细观察，动物们就会向我们‘诉说’它们的需求。”
So, despite the word ‘koala’ meaning 'no drink' or 'no water' in the Aboriginal language, it seems that even these sleepy creatures do need a drink sometimes.
因此，尽管在澳大利亚原住民的语言中，“考拉”一词意为“不喝水”，但事实证明，即便是这些嗜睡的小家伙，有时也需要补充水分。
And if we’re to encourage them to flourish, we need to conserve their habitat.
而如果我们想要让考拉种群得以繁衍壮大，就必须保护好它们的栖息地。